[
{"question": "游游", "response": "Bolivia" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Peru" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Argentina" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Burkina Faso" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Armenia" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Canad치" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Emiratos 츼rabes Unidos" }, 
{"question": "游뷣릖", "response": "Austria" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Bar칠in" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Bulgaria" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "Costa de Marfil" }, 
{"question": "游뻟릖", "response": "China" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Jap칩n" }, 
{"question": "游뾇릖", "response": "Alemania" },
{"question": "游쐟릖", "response": "Letonia" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Puerto Rico" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Brasil" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "Burkina Faso" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Panam치" }, 
{"question": "游좷릖", "response": "Tayikist치n" }, 
{"question": "游섫릖", "response": "Grecia" }, 
{"question": "游좷릖", "response": "Togo" }, 
{"question": "游쓇릖", "response": "Birmania" }, 
{"question": "游쓇릖", "response": "Marruecos" }, 
{"question": "游游", "response": "N칤ger" }, 
{"question": "游왫릖", "response": "Paraguay" }
]